STEPHANIE RODRIGUEZ

(773) 243-9524 | steph99rodriguez@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/stephanie99rodriguez

PROFILE

Tenacious programmer with 2+ years of experience in Python and SQL, seeking to create new and experimental projects. Experienced in transforming data using Python as well as encouraging and training teammates through one-on-one sessions to achieve higher productivity in a fast-paced work environment.

EDUCATION

Lovola University Chicago

Bachelor of Business Administration in Information Systems Bachelor of Science in Computer Science Expected May 2021

GPA: 3.89

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming: Python, SQL, Java, HTML/CSS

Software and Tools: Tableau, MAMP, MS Excel, MS Access, Database Modeling

Languages: Spanish (intermediate working proficiency), Japanese (limited working proficiency)

EXPERIENCE

Kemper Insurance

Business Transformation and Finance Intern

November 2019 - Current

- Coding a project to efficiently collect company data to generate quarterly financial reports using openpyxl, pandas, and data frames in Python
- Transitioned company data using Python and SQL from excel reporting to AWS S3, Redshift, and Tableau

Department of Computer Science, Loyola University Chicago

Computer Science Tutor

August 2019 - March 2020

- Tutored computer science students in a range of classes, e.g., Data Structures and Applications and Object-Oriented Programming, at the introductory and at the intermediate levels
- Reviewed and debugged other students' code in programming languages, including Java and Python

Victoria's Secret & Pink

Sales Associate, Angel Card Lead August 2017 – October 2019

- Held the store record for the number of credit card applications opened in a 4-week period as well as helping the store become the top credit earner in the Chicago district
- Motivated and trained coworkers to open credit card applications to set new personal records and lead the store to increase applications by 214% from the previous year

Youth About Business

Chicago Ambassador and Head Volunteer

September 2015 – June 2016

• Selected by the Director of Youth About Business to organize shoe drives in Chicago and gathered more than 600 pairs of shoes in a three-month period